[
    {
        "id": "words2 - 0",
        "front": "大腸",
        "back": "대장"
    },
    {
        "id": "words2 - 1",
        "front": "後者",
        "back": "후자"
    },
    {
        "id": "words2 - 2",
        "front": "流通",
        "back": "유통"
    },
    {
        "id": "words2 - 3",
        "front": "駐車",
        "back": "주차"
    },
    {
        "id": "words2 - 4",
        "front": "儀式",
        "back": "의식"
    },
    {
        "id": "words2 - 5",
        "front": "主義",
        "back": "주의"
    },
    {
        "id": "words2 - 6",
        "front": "主因",
        "back": "주인"
    },
    {
        "id": "words2 - 7",
        "front": "住所",
        "back": "주소"
    },
    {
        "id": "words2 - 8",
        "front": "注目",
        "back": "주목"
    },
    {
        "id": "words2 - 9",
        "front": "尾註",
        "back": "미주"
    },
    {
        "id": "words2 - 10",
        "front": "正義",
        "back": "정의"
    },
    {
        "id": "words2 - 11",
        "front": "會議",
        "back": "회의"
    },
    {
        "id": "words2 - 12",
        "front": "必要",
        "back": "필요"
    },
    {
        "id": "words2 - 13",
        "front": "必然",
        "back": "필연"
    },
    {
        "id": "words2 - 14",
        "front": "重要",
        "back": "중요"
    },
    {
        "id": "words2 - 15",
        "front": "腰折腹痛",
        "back": "요절복통"
    },
    {
        "id": "words2 - 16",
        "front": "本格",
        "back": "본격"
    },
    {
        "id": "words2 - 17",
        "front": "根本",
        "back": "근본"
    },
    {
        "id": "words2 - 18",
        "front": "人格",
        "back": "인격"
    },
    {
        "id": "words2 - 19",
        "front": "各自",
        "back": "각자"
    },
    {
        "id": "words2 - 20",
        "front": "主客",
        "back": "주객"
    },
    {
        "id": "words2 - 21",
        "front": "單語",
        "back": "한자"
    },
    {
        "id": "words2 - 22",
        "front": "簡單",
        "back": "간단"
    },
    {
        "id": "words2 - 23",
        "front": "戰爭",
        "back": "전쟁"
    },
    {
        "id": "words2 - 24",
        "front": "言語",
        "back": "언어"
    },
    {
        "id": "words2 - 25",
        "front": "試驗",
        "back": "시험"
    },
    {
        "id": "words2 - 26",
        "front": "試圖",
        "back": "시도"
    },
    {
        "id": "words2 - 27",
        "front": "方式",
        "back": "방식"
    },
    {
        "id": "words2 - 28",
        "front": "經驗",
        "back": "경험"
    },
    {
        "id": "words2 - 29",
        "front": "危險",
        "back": "위험"
    },
    {
        "id": "words2 - 30",
        "front": "檢察",
        "back": "검찰"
    },
    {
        "id": "words2 - 31",
        "front": "劍道",
        "back": "검도"
    },
    {
        "id": "words2 - 32",
        "front": "每日",
        "back": "매일"
    },
    {
        "id": "words2 - 33",
        "front": "每回",
        "back": "매회"
    },
    {
        "id": "words2 - 34",
        "front": "梅花",
        "back": "매화"
    },
    {
        "id": "words2 - 35",
        "front": "後悔",
        "back": "후회"
    },
    {
        "id": "words2 - 36",
        "front": "父母",
        "back": "부모"
    },
    {
        "id": "words2 - 37",
        "front": "當然",
        "back": "당연"
    },
    {
        "id": "words2 - 38",
        "front": "食堂",
        "back": "식당"
    },
    {
        "id": "words2 - 39",
        "front": "正當",
        "back": "정당"
    },
    {
        "id": "words2 - 40",
        "front": "政黨",
        "back": "정당"
    },
    {
        "id": "words2 - 41",
        "front": "高尙",
        "back": "고상"
    },
    {
        "id": "words2 - 42",
        "front": "衣裳",
        "back": "의상"
    },
    {
        "id": "words2 - 43",
        "front": "常識",
        "back": "상식"
    },
    {
        "id": "words2 - 44",
        "front": "報償",
        "back": "보상"
    },
    {
        "id": "words2 - 45",
        "front": "賞品",
        "back": "상품"
    },
    {
        "id": "words2 - 46",
        "front": "掌甲",
        "back": "장갑"
    },
    {
        "id": "words2 - 47",
        "front": "必然",
        "back": "필연"
    },
    {
        "id": "words2 - 48",
        "front": "燃料",
        "back": "연료"
    },
    {
        "id": "words2 - 49",
        "front": "交流",
        "back": "교류"
    },
    {
        "id": "words2 - 50",
        "front": "交代",
        "back": "교대"
    },
    {
        "id": "words2 - 51",
        "front": "學校",
        "back": "학교"
    },
    {
        "id": "words2 - 52",
        "front": "比較",
        "back": "비교"
    },
    {
        "id": "words2 - 53",
        "front": "效果",
        "back": "효과"
    },
    {
        "id": "words2 - 54",
        "front": "文化圈",
        "back": "문화권"
    },
    {
        "id": "words2 - 55",
        "front": "文章",
        "back": "문장"
    },
    {
        "id": "words2 - 56",
        "front": "指紋",
        "back": "지문"
    },
    {
        "id": "words2 - 57",
        "front": "文化",
        "back": "문화"
    },
    {
        "id": "words2 - 58",
        "front": "百貨店",
        "back": "백화점"
    },
    {
        "id": "words2 - 59",
        "front": "花草",
        "back": "화초"
    },
    {
        "id": "words2 - 60",
        "front": "圈域",
        "back": "권역"
    },
    {
        "id": "words2 - 61",
        "front": "上卷",
        "back": "상권"
    },
    {
        "id": "words2 - 62",
        "front": "證卷",
        "back": "증권"
    },
    {
        "id": "words2 - 63",
        "front": "卷鬪",
        "back": "권투"
    },
    {
        "id": "words2 - 64",
        "front": "西洋",
        "back": "서양"
    },
    {
        "id": "words2 - 65",
        "front": "東西南北",
        "back": "동서남북"
    },
    {
        "id": "words2 - 66",
        "front": "海洋",
        "back": "해양"
    },
    {
        "id": "words2 - 67",
        "front": "養育",
        "back": "양육"
    },
    {
        "id": "words2 - 68",
        "front": "牛羊馬",
        "back": "우양마"
    },
    {
        "id": "words2 - 69",
        "front": "分別",
        "back": "분별"
    },
    {
        "id": "words2 - 70",
        "front": "用途",
        "back": "용도"
    },
    {
        "id": "words2 - 71",
        "front": "關係",
        "back": "관계"
    },
    {
        "id": "words2 - 72",
        "front": "別途",
        "back": "별도"
    },
    {
        "id": "words2 - 73",
        "front": "關聯",
        "back": "관련"
    },
    {
        "id": "words2 - 74",
        "front": "係長",
        "back": "계장"
    },
    {
        "id": "words2 - 75",
        "front": "系列",
        "back": "계열"
    },
    {
        "id": "words2 - 76",
        "front": "韻文",
        "back": "운문"
    },
    {
        "id": "words2 - 77",
        "front": "音韻",
        "back": "음운"
    },
    {
        "id": "words2 - 78",
        "front": "人員",
        "back": "인원"
    },
    {
        "id": "words2 - 79",
        "front": "文學",
        "back": "문학"
    },
    {
        "id": "words2 - 80",
        "front": "圓形",
        "back": "원형"
    },
    {
        "id": "words2 - 81",
        "front": "後悔",
        "back": "후회"
    },
    {
        "id": "words2 - 82",
        "front": "前者",
        "back": "전자"
    },
    {
        "id": "words2 - 83",
        "front": "登場",
        "back": "등장"
    },
    {
        "id": "words2 - 84",
        "front": "登山",
        "back": "등산"
    },
    {
        "id": "words2 - 85",
        "front": "電燈",
        "back": "전등"
    },
    {
        "id": "words2 - 86",
        "front": "場所",
        "back": "장소"
    },
    {
        "id": "words2 - 87",
        "front": "證明",
        "back": "증명"
    },
    {
        "id": "words2 - 88",
        "front": "太陽",
        "back": "태양"
    },
    {
        "id": "words2 - 89",
        "front": "人物",
        "back": "인물"
    },
    {
        "id": "words2 - 90",
        "front": "太陽",
        "back": "태양"
    },
    {
        "id": "words2 - 91",
        "front": "人物",
        "back": "인물"
    },
    {
        "id": "words2 - 92",
        "front": "事物",
        "back": "사물"
    },
    {
        "id": "words2 - 93",
        "front": "勿論",
        "back": "물론"
    },
    {
        "id": "words2 - 94",
        "front": "意味",
        "back": "의미"
    },
    {
        "id": "words2 - 95",
        "front": "意志",
        "back": "의지"
    },
    {
        "id": "words2 - 96",
        "front": "音樂",
        "back": "음악"
    },
    {
        "id": "words2 - 97",
        "front": "甘味",
        "back": "감미"
    },
    {
        "id": "words2 - 98",
        "front": "未來",
        "back": "미래"
    },
    {
        "id": "words2 - 99",
        "front": "民族",
        "back": "민족"
    },
    {
        "id": "words2 - 100",
        "front": "賤民",
        "back": "천민"
    },
    {
        "id": "words2 - 101",
        "front": "貴族",
        "back": "귀족"
    },
    {
        "id": "words2 - 102",
        "front": "國旗",
        "back": "국기"
    },
    {
        "id": "words2 - 103",
        "front": "旅行",
        "back": "여행"
    },
    {
        "id": "words2 - 104",
        "front": "施行",
        "back": "시행"
    },
    {
        "id": "words2 - 105",
        "front": "世界",
        "back": "세계"
    },
    {
        "id": "words2 - 106",
        "front": "世上",
        "back": "세상"
    },
    {
        "id": "words2 - 107",
        "front": "限界",
        "back": "한계"
    },
    {
        "id": "words2 - 108",
        "front": "仲介",
        "back": "중개"
    },
    {
        "id": "words2 - 109",
        "front": "平和",
        "back": "평화"
    },
    {
        "id": "words2 - 110",
        "front": "平平",
        "back": "평평"
    },
    {
        "id": "words2 - 111",
        "front": "評價",
        "back": "평가"
    },
    {
        "id": "words2 - 112",
        "front": "十坪",
        "back": "10평"
    },
    {
        "id": "words2 - 113",
        "front": "十坪",
        "back": "조화"
    },
    {
        "id": "words2 - 114",
        "front": "滿期",
        "back": "만기"
    },
    {
        "id": "words2 - 115",
        "front": "滿足",
        "back": "만족"
    },
    {
        "id": "words2 - 116",
        "front": "時期",
        "back": "시기"
    },
    {
        "id": "words2 - 117",
        "front": "基本",
        "back": "기본"
    },
    {
        "id": "words2 - 118",
        "front": "國旗",
        "back": "국기"
    },
    {
        "id": "words2 - 119",
        "front": "基本",
        "back": "기본"
    },
    {
        "id": "words2 - 120",
        "front": "其他",
        "back": "기타"
    },
    {
        "id": "words2 - 121",
        "front": "欺滿",
        "back": "기만"
    },
    {
        "id": "words2 - 122",
        "front": "願望",
        "back": "원망"
    },
    {
        "id": "words2 - 123",
        "front": "所願",
        "back": "소원"
    },
    {
        "id": "words2 - 124",
        "front": "根源",
        "back": "근원"
    },
    {
        "id": "words2 - 125",
        "front": "亡身",
        "back": "망신"
    },
    {
        "id": "words2 - 126",
        "front": "妄言",
        "back": "망언"
    },
    {
        "id": "words2 - 127",
        "front": "勿忘草",
        "back": "물망초"
    },
    {
        "id": "words2 - 128",
        "front": "茫茫大海",
        "back": "망망대해"
    },
    {
        "id": "words2 - 129",
        "front": "政府",
        "back": "정부"
    },
    {
        "id": "words2 - 130",
        "front": "政治",
        "back": "정치"
    },
    {
        "id": "words2 - 131",
        "front": "整理",
        "back": "정리"
    },
    {
        "id": "words2 - 132",
        "front": "正當",
        "back": "정당"
    },
    {
        "id": "words2 - 133",
        "front": "征伐",
        "back": "정벌"
    },
    {
        "id": "words2 - 134",
        "front": "發付",
        "back": "발부"
    },
    {
        "id": "words2 - 135",
        "front": "添附",
        "back": "첨부"
    },
    {
        "id": "words2 - 136",
        "front": "符合",
        "back": "부합"
    },
    {
        "id": "words2 - 137",
        "front": "腐敗",
        "back": "부패"
    },
    {
        "id": "words2 - 138",
        "front": "物品",
        "back": "물품"
    },
    {
        "id": "words2 - 139",
        "front": "器物",
        "back": "기물"
    },
    {
        "id": "words2 - 140",
        "front": "筆者",
        "back": "필자"
    },
    {
        "id": "words2 - 141",
        "front": "筆記",
        "back": "필기"
    },
    {
        "id": "words2 - 142",
        "front": "文書",
        "back": "문서"
    },
    {
        "id": "words2 - 143",
        "front": "畫家",
        "back": "화가"
    },
    {
        "id": "words2 - 144",
        "front": "劃一",
        "back": "획일"
    },
    {
        "id": "words2 - 145",
        "front": "苦悶",
        "back": "고민"
    },
    {
        "id": "words2 - 146",
        "front": "苦痛",
        "back": "고통"
    },
    {
        "id": "words2 - 147",
        "front": "古典",
        "back": "고전"
    },
    {
        "id": "words2 - 148",
        "front": "故鄕",
        "back": "고향"
    },
    {
        "id": "words2 - 149",
        "front": "姑母",
        "back": "고모"
    },
    {
        "id": "words2 - 150",
        "front": "固定",
        "back": "고정"
    },
    {
        "id": "words2 - 151",
        "front": "枯渴",
        "back": "고갈"
    },
    {
        "id": "words2 - 152",
        "front": "達觀",
        "back": "달관"
    },
    {
        "id": "words2 - 153",
        "front": "到達",
        "back": "도달"
    },
    {
        "id": "words2 - 154",
        "front": "觀察",
        "back": "관찰"
    },
    {
        "id": "words2 - 155",
        "front": "權力",
        "back": "권력"
    },
    {
        "id": "words2 - 156",
        "front": "勸告",
        "back": "권고"
    },
    {
        "id": "words2 - 157",
        "front": "條件",
        "back": "조건"
    },
    {
        "id": "words2 - 158",
        "front": "條目",
        "back": "조목"
    },
    {
        "id": "words2 - 159",
        "front": "物件",
        "back": "물건"
    },
    {
        "id": "words2 - 160",
        "front": "背景",
        "back": "배경"
    },
    {
        "id": "words2 - 161",
        "front": "背信",
        "back": "배신"
    },
    {
        "id": "words2 - 162",
        "front": "南北",
        "back": "남북"
    },
    {
        "id": "words2 - 163",
        "front": "比較",
        "back": "비교"
    },
    {
        "id": "words2 - 164",
        "front": "風景",
        "back": "풍경"
    },
    {
        "id": "words2 - 165",
        "front": "上京",
        "back": "상경"
    },
    {
        "id": "words2 - 166",
        "front": "道家",
        "back": "도가"
    },
    {
        "id": "words2 - 167",
        "front": "道理",
        "back": "도리"
    },
    {
        "id": "words2 - 168",
        "front": "家屋",
        "back": "가옥"
    },
    {
        "id": "words2 - 169",
        "front": "表明",
        "back": "표명"
    },
    {
        "id": "words2 - 170",
        "front": "表面",
        "back": "표면"
    },
    {
        "id": "words2 - 171",
        "front": "明示",
        "back": "명시"
    },
    {
        "id": "words2 - 172",
        "front": "恒常",
        "back": "항상"
    },
    {
        "id": "words2 - 173",
        "front": "恒星",
        "back": "항성"
    },
    {
        "id": "words2 - 174",
        "front": "常識",
        "back": "상식"
    },
    {
        "id": "words2 - 175",
        "front": "自由",
        "back": "자유"
    },
    {
        "id": "words2 - 176",
        "front": "自身",
        "back": "자신"
    },
    {
        "id": "words2 - 177",
        "front": "理由",
        "back": "이유"
    },
    {
        "id": "words2 - 178",
        "front": "注油",
        "back": "주유"
    },
    {
        "id": "words2 - 179",
        "front": "宇宙",
        "back": "우주"
    },
    {
        "id": "words2 - 180",
        "front": "抽出",
        "back": "추출"
    },
    {
        "id": "words2 - 181",
        "front": "地軸",
        "back": "지축"
    },
    {
        "id": "words2 - 182",
        "front": "眞理",
        "back": "진리"
    },
    {
        "id": "words2 - 183",
        "front": "眞心",
        "back": "진심"
    },
    {
        "id": "words2 - 184",
        "front": "道里",
        "back": "도리"
    },
    {
        "id": "words2 - 185",
        "front": "野望",
        "back": "야망"
    },
    {
        "id": "words2 - 186",
        "front": "與野",
        "back": "여야"
    },
    {
        "id": "words2 - 187",
        "front": "素望",
        "back": "소망"
    },
    {
        "id": "words2 - 188",
        "front": "祖國",
        "back": "조국"
    },
    {
        "id": "words2 - 189",
        "front": "祖父",
        "back": "조부"
    },
    {
        "id": "words2 - 190",
        "front": "協助",
        "back": "협조"
    },
    {
        "id": "words2 - 191",
        "front": "粗惡",
        "back": "조악"
    },
    {
        "id": "words2 - 192",
        "front": "組織",
        "back": "조직"
    },
    {
        "id": "words2 - 193",
        "front": "租稅",
        "back": "조세"
    },
    {
        "id": "words2 - 194",
        "front": "空間",
        "back": "공간"
    },
    {
        "id": "words2 - 195",
        "front": "空想",
        "back": "공상"
    },
    {
        "id": "words2 - 196",
        "front": "工場",
        "back": "공장"
    },
    {
        "id": "words2 - 197",
        "front": "功勞",
        "back": "공로"
    },
    {
        "id": "words2 - 198",
        "front": "攻防",
        "back": "공방"
    },
    {
        "id": "words2 - 199",
        "front": "江山",
        "back": "강산"
    },
    {
        "id": "words2 - 200",
        "front": "分類",
        "back": "분류"
    },
    {
        "id": "words2 - 201",
        "front": "分別",
        "back": "분별"
    },
    {
        "id": "words2 - 202",
        "front": "花盆",
        "back": "화분"
    },
    {
        "id": "words2 - 203",
        "front": "粉塵",
        "back": "분진"
    },
    {
        "id": "words2 - 204",
        "front": "紛紛",
        "back": "분분"
    },
    {
        "id": "words2 - 205",
        "front": "人類",
        "back": "인류"
    },
    {
        "id": "words2 - 206",
        "front": "職長",
        "back": "직장"
    },
    {
        "id": "words2 - 207",
        "front": "職員",
        "back": "직원"
    },
    {
        "id": "words2 - 208",
        "front": "組織",
        "back": "조직"
    },
    {
        "id": "words2 - 209",
        "front": "認識",
        "back": "인식"
    },
    {
        "id": "words2 - 210",
        "front": "部下",
        "back": "부하"
    },
    {
        "id": "words2 - 211",
        "front": "部落",
        "back": "부락"
    },
    {
        "id": "words2 - 212",
        "front": "部署",
        "back": "부서"
    },
    {
        "id": "words2 - 213",
        "front": "都市",
        "back": "도시"
    },
    {
        "id": "words2 - 214",
        "front": "郊外",
        "back": "교외"
    },
    {
        "id": "words2 - 215",
        "front": "先輩",
        "back": "선배"
    },
    {
        "id": "words2 - 216",
        "front": "先頭",
        "back": "선두"
    },
    {
        "id": "words2 - 217",
        "front": "後排",
        "back": "후배"
    },
    {
        "id": "words2 - 218",
        "front": "排出",
        "back": "배출"
    },
    {
        "id": "words2 - 219",
        "front": "徘徊",
        "back": "배회"
    },
    {
        "id": "words2 - 220",
        "front": "是是非非",
        "back": "시시비비"
    },
    {
        "id": "words2 - 221",
        "front": "悲感",
        "back": "비감"
    },
    {
        "id": "words2 - 222",
        "front": "敎師",
        "back": "교사"
    },
    {
        "id": "words2 - 223",
        "front": "敎育",
        "back": "교육"
    },
    {
        "id": "words2 - 224",
        "front": "師父",
        "back": "사부"
    },
    {
        "id": "words2 - 225",
        "front": "態度",
        "back": "태도"
    },
    {
        "id": "words2 - 226",
        "front": "狀態",
        "back": "상태"
    },
    {
        "id": "words2 - 227",
        "front": "可能",
        "back": "가능"
    },
    {
        "id": "words2 - 228",
        "front": "熊女",
        "back": "웅녀"
    },
    {
        "id": "words2 - 229",
        "front": "程度",
        "back": "정도"
    },
    {
        "id": "words2 - 230",
        "front": "共同",
        "back": "공동"
    },
    {
        "id": "words2 - 231",
        "front": "共有",
        "back": "공유"
    },
    {
        "id": "words2 - 232",
        "front": "提供",
        "back": "제공"
    },
    {
        "id": "words2 - 233",
        "front": "恭敬",
        "back": "공경"
    },
    {
        "id": "words2 - 234",
        "front": "同時",
        "back": "동시"
    },
    {
        "id": "words2 - 235",
        "front": "方向",
        "back": "방향"
    },
    {
        "id": "words2 - 236",
        "front": "方式",
        "back": "방식"
    },
    {
        "id": "words2 - 237",
        "front": "防止",
        "back": "방지"
    },
    {
        "id": "words2 - 238",
        "front": "放學",
        "back": "방학"
    },
    {
        "id": "words2 - 239",
        "front": "妨害",
        "back": "방해"
    },
    {
        "id": "words2 - 240",
        "front": "訪問",
        "back": "방문"
    },
    {
        "id": "words2 - 241",
        "front": "傍觀",
        "back": "방관"
    },
    {
        "id": "words2 - 242",
        "front": "向後",
        "back": "향후"
    },
    {
        "id": "words2 - 243",
        "front": "高尚",
        "back": "고상"
    },
    {
        "id": "words2 - 244",
        "front": "協商",
        "back": "협상"
    },
    {
        "id": "words2 - 245",
        "front": "展開",
        "back": "전개"
    },
    {
        "id": "words2 - 246",
        "front": "展示",
        "back": "전시"
    },
    {
        "id": "words2 - 247",
        "front": "尾行",
        "back": "미행"
    },
    {
        "id": "words2 - 248",
        "front": "居住",
        "back": "거주"
    },
    {
        "id": "words2 - 249",
        "front": "開放",
        "back": "개방"
    },
    {
        "id": "words2 - 250",
        "front": "新鮮",
        "back": "신선"
    },
    {
        "id": "words2 - 251",
        "front": "新聞",
        "back": "신문"
    },
    {
        "id": "words2 - 252",
        "front": "朝鮮",
        "back": "조선"
    },
    {
        "id": "words2 - 253",
        "front": "錯覺",
        "back": "착각"
    },
    {
        "id": "words2 - 254",
        "front": "錯視",
        "back": "착시"
    },
    {
        "id": "words2 - 255",
        "front": "惜別",
        "back": "석별"
    },
    {
        "id": "words2 - 256",
        "front": "自覺",
        "back": "자각"
    },
    {
        "id": "words2 - 257",
        "front": "盲目",
        "back": "맹목"
    },
    {
        "id": "words2 - 258",
        "front": "亡身",
        "back": "망신"
    },
    {
        "id": "words2 - 259",
        "front": "野望",
        "back": "야망"
    },
    {
        "id": "words2 - 260",
        "front": "目不忍見",
        "back": "목불인견"
    },
    {
        "id": "words2 - 261",
        "front": "速度",
        "back": "속도"
    },
    {
        "id": "words2 - 262",
        "front": "速力",
        "back": "속력"
    },
    {
        "id": "words2 - 263",
        "front": "約束",
        "back": "약속"
    },
    {
        "id": "words2 - 264",
        "front": "傳達",
        "back": "전달"
    },
    {
        "id": "words2 - 265",
        "front": "傳統",
        "back": "전통"
    },
    {
        "id": "words2 - 266",
        "front": "專攻",
        "back": "전공"
    },
    {
        "id": "words2 - 267",
        "front": "運轉",
        "back": "운전"
    },
    {
        "id": "words2 - 268",
        "front": "移轉",
        "back": "이전"
    },
    {
        "id": "words2 - 269",
        "front": "團體",
        "back": "단체"
    },
    {
        "id": "words2 - 270",
        "front": "到達",
        "back": "도달"
    },
    {
        "id": "words2 - 271",
        "front": "計算",
        "back": "계산"
    },
    {
        "id": "words2 - 272",
        "front": "會計",
        "back": "회계"
    },
    {
        "id": "words2 - 273",
        "front": "算數",
        "back": "산수"
    },
    {
        "id": "words2 - 274",
        "front": "制限",
        "back": "제한"
    },
    {
        "id": "words2 - 275",
        "front": "制約",
        "back": "제약"
    },
    {
        "id": "words2 - 276",
        "front": "製品",
        "back": "제품"
    },
    {
        "id": "words2 - 277",
        "front": "限界",
        "back": "한계"
    },
    {
        "id": "words2 - 278",
        "front": "選擇",
        "back": "선택"
    },
    {
        "id": "words2 - 279",
        "front": "選擧",
        "back": "선거"
    },
    {
        "id": "words2 - 280",
        "front": "擇一",
        "back": "택일"
    },
    {
        "id": "words2 - 281",
        "front": "解釋",
        "back": "해석"
    },
    {
        "id": "words2 - 282",
        "front": "通譯",
        "back": "통역"
    },
    {
        "id": "words2 - 283",
        "front": "效率",
        "back": "효율"
    },
    {
        "id": "words2 - 284",
        "front": "比率",
        "back": "비율"
    },
    {
        "id": "words2 - 285",
        "front": "率先",
        "back": "솔선"
    },
    {
        "id": "words2 - 286",
        "front": "設置",
        "back": "설치"
    },
    {
        "id": "words2 - 287",
        "front": "施設",
        "back": "시설"
    },
    {
        "id": "words2 - 288",
        "front": "放置",
        "back": "방치"
    },
    {
        "id": "words2 - 289",
        "front": "價値",
        "back": "가치"
    },
    {
        "id": "words2 - 290",
        "front": "正直",
        "back": "정직"
    },
    {
        "id": "words2 - 291",
        "front": "植物",
        "back": "식물"
    },
    {
        "id": "words2 - 292",
        "front": "加害者",
        "back": "가해자"
    },
    {
        "id": "words2 - 293",
        "front": "加味",
        "back": "가미"
    },
    {
        "id": "words2 - 294",
        "front": "高架道路",
        "back": "고가도로"
    },
    {
        "id": "words2 - 295",
        "front": "被害",
        "back": "피해"
    },
    {
        "id": "words2 - 296",
        "front": "分割",
        "back": "분할"
    },
    {
        "id": "words2 - 297",
        "front": "警察署",
        "back": "경찰서"
    },
    {
        "id": "words2 - 298",
        "front": "警戒",
        "back": "경계"
    },
    {
        "id": "words2 - 299",
        "front": "恭敬",
        "back": "공경"
    },
    {
        "id": "words2 - 300",
        "front": "驚氣",
        "back": "경기"
    },
    {
        "id": "words2 - 301",
        "front": "觀察",
        "back": "관찰"
    },
    {
        "id": "words2 - 302",
        "front": "祭器",
        "back": "제기"
    },
    {
        "id": "words2 - 303",
        "front": "國際",
        "back": "국제"
    },
    {
        "id": "words2 - 304",
        "front": "部署",
        "back": "부서"
    },
    {
        "id": "words2 - 305",
        "front": "對答",
        "back": "대답"
    },
    {
        "id": "words2 - 306",
        "front": "相對",
        "back": "상대"
    },
    {
        "id": "words2 - 307",
        "front": "黙黙不答",
        "back": "묵묵부답"
    },
    {
        "id": "words2 - 308",
        "front": "結合",
        "back": "결합"
    },
    {
        "id": "words2 - 309",
        "front": "被疑者",
        "back": "피의자"
    },
    {
        "id": "words2 - 310",
        "front": "被告",
        "back": "피고"
    },
    {
        "id": "words2 - 311",
        "front": "皮相",
        "back": "피상"
    },
    {
        "id": "words2 - 312",
        "front": "疲勞",
        "back": "피로"
    },
    {
        "id": "words2 - 313",
        "front": "破壞",
        "back": "파괴"
    },
    {
        "id": "words2 - 314",
        "front": "波紋",
        "back": "파문"
    },
    {
        "id": "words2 - 315",
        "front": "疑問",
        "back": "의문"
    },
    {
        "id": "words2 - 316",
        "front": "抑鬱",
        "back": "억울"
    },
    {
        "id": "words2 - 317",
        "front": "抑制",
        "back": "억제"
    },
    {
        "id": "words2 - 318",
        "front": "印刷",
        "back": "인쇄"
    },
    {
        "id": "words2 - 319",
        "front": "鬱火病",
        "back": "울화병"
    },
    {
        "id": "words2 - 320",
        "front": "犯人",
        "back": "범인"
    },
    {
        "id": "words2 - 321",
        "front": "범행",
        "back": "犯行"
    },
    {
        "id": "words2 - 322",
        "front": "危機",
        "back": "위기"
    },
    {
        "id": "words2 - 323",
        "front": "狂人",
        "back": "광인"
    },
    {
        "id": "words2 - 324",
        "front": "博士",
        "back": "박사"
    },
    {
        "id": "words2 - 325",
        "front": "淺薄",
        "back": "천박"
    },
    {
        "id": "words2 - 326",
        "front": "名簿",
        "back": "명부"
    },
    {
        "id": "words2 - 327",
        "front": "旣存",
        "back": "기존"
    },
    {
        "id": "words2 - 328",
        "front": "旣成",
        "back": "기성"
    },
    {
        "id": "words2 - 329",
        "front": "卽時",
        "back": "즉시"
    },
    {
        "id": "words2 - 330",
        "front": "存在",
        "back": "존재"
    },
    {
        "id": "words2 - 331",
        "front": "科學",
        "back": "과학"
    },
    {
        "id": "words2 - 332",
        "front": "分科",
        "back": "분과"
    },
    {
        "id": "words2 - 333",
        "front": "學問",
        "back": "학문"
    },
    {
        "id": "words2 - 334",
        "front": "成果",
        "back": "성과"
    },
    {
        "id": "words2 - 335",
        "front": "完成",
        "back": "완성"
    },
    {
        "id": "words2 - 336",
        "front": "誠實",
        "back": "성실"
    },
    {
        "id": "words2 - 337",
        "front": "盛大",
        "back": "성대"
    },
    {
        "id": "words2 - 338",
        "front": "城門",
        "back": "성문"
    },
    {
        "id": "words2 - 339",
        "front": "結果",
        "back": "결과"
    },
    {
        "id": "words2 - 340",
        "front": "果敢",
        "back": "과감"
    },
    {
        "id": "words2 - 341",
        "front": "課題",
        "back": "과제"
    },
    {
        "id": "words2 - 342",
        "front": "菓子",
        "back": "과자"
    },
    {
        "id": "words2 - 343",
        "front": "反響",
        "back": "반향"
    },
    {
        "id": "words2 - 344",
        "front": "反對",
        "back": "반대"
    },
    {
        "id": "words2 - 345",
        "front": "返送",
        "back": "반송"
    },
    {
        "id": "words2 - 346",
        "front": "白飯",
        "back": "백반"
    },
    {
        "id": "words2 - 347",
        "front": "看板",
        "back": "간판"
    },
    {
        "id": "words2 - 348",
        "front": "出版",
        "back": "출판"
    },
    {
        "id": "words2 - 349",
        "front": "音響",
        "back": "음향"
    },
    {
        "id": "words2 - 350",
        "front": "故鄕",
        "back": "고향"
    },
    {
        "id": "words2 - 351",
        "front": "提示",
        "back": "제시"
    },
    {
        "id": "words2 - 352",
        "front": "提供",
        "back": "제공"
    },
    {
        "id": "words2 - 353",
        "front": "問題",
        "back": "문제"
    },
    {
        "id": "words2 - 354",
        "front": "是是非非",
        "back": "시시비비"
    },
    {
        "id": "words2 - 355",
        "front": "明示",
        "back": "명시"
    },
    {
        "id": "words2 - 356",
        "front": "非可逆",
        "back": "비가역"
    },
    {
        "id": "words2 - 357",
        "front": "可能",
        "back": "가능"
    },
    {
        "id": "words2 - 358",
        "front": "江河",
        "back": "강하"
    },
    {
        "id": "words2 - 359",
        "front": "逆說",
        "back": "역설"
    },
    {
        "id": "words2 - 360",
        "front": "始作",
        "back": "시작"
    },
    {
        "id": "words2 - 361",
        "front": "原始",
        "back": "원시"
    },
    {
        "id": "words2 - 362",
        "front": "作品",
        "back": "작품"
    },
    {
        "id": "words2 - 363",
        "front": "昨年",
        "back": "작년"
    },
    {
        "id": "words2 - 364",
        "front": "威脅",
        "back": "위협"
    },
    {
        "id": "words2 - 365",
        "front": "權威",
        "back": "권위"
    },
    {
        "id": "words2 - 366",
        "front": "脅迫",
        "back": "협박"
    },
    {
        "id": "words2 - 367",
        "front": "協商",
        "back": "협상"
    },
    {
        "id": "words2 - 368",
        "front": "現狀",
        "back": "현상"
    },
    {
        "id": "words2 - 369",
        "front": "再現",
        "back": "재현"
    },
    {
        "id": "words2 - 370",
        "front": "狀況",
        "back": "상황"
    },
    {
        "id": "words2 - 371",
        "front": "滅亡",
        "back": "멸망"
    },
    {
        "id": "words2 - 372",
        "front": "破滅",
        "back": "파멸"
    },
    {
        "id": "words2 - 373",
        "front": "亡身",
        "back": "망신"
    },
    {
        "id": "words2 - 374",
        "front": "盲目",
        "back": "맹목"
    },
    {
        "id": "words2 - 375",
        "front": "增加",
        "back": "증가"
    },
    {
        "id": "words2 - 376",
        "front": "增設",
        "back": "증설"
    },
    {
        "id": "words2 - 377",
        "front": "憎惡",
        "back": "증오"
    },
    {
        "id": "words2 - 378",
        "front": "贈與",
        "back": "증여"
    },
    {
        "id": "words2 - 379",
        "front": "加害者",
        "back": "가해자"
    },
    {
        "id": "words2 - 380",
        "front": "運動量",
        "back": "운동량"
    },
    {
        "id": "words2 - 381",
        "front": "運轉",
        "back": "운전"
    },
    {
        "id": "words2 - 382",
        "front": "軍人",
        "back": "군인"
    },
    {
        "id": "words2 - 383",
        "front": "動作",
        "back": "동작"
    },
    {
        "id": "words2 - 384",
        "front": "東西",
        "back": "동서"
    },
    {
        "id": "words2 - 385",
        "front": "兒童",
        "back": "아동"
    },
    {
        "id": "words2 - 386",
        "front": "多量",
        "back": "다량"
    },
    {
        "id": "words2 - 387",
        "front": "危險",
        "back": "위험"
    },
    {
        "id": "words2 - 388",
        "front": "危急",
        "back": "위급"
    },
    {
        "id": "words2 - 389",
        "front": "險惡",
        "back": "험악"
    },
    {
        "id": "words2 - 390",
        "front": "若干",
        "back": "약간"
    },
    {
        "id": "words2 - 391",
        "front": "明若觀火",
        "back": "명약관화"
    },
    {
        "id": "words2 - 392",
        "front": "干與",
        "back": "간여"
    },
    {
        "id": "words2 - 393",
        "front": "發刊",
        "back": "발간"
    },
    {
        "id": "words2 - 394",
        "front": "長點",
        "back": "장점"
    },
    {
        "id": "words2 - 395",
        "front": "長幼有序",
        "back": "장유유서"
    },
    {
        "id": "words2 - 396",
        "front": "黑點",
        "back": "흑점"
    },
    {
        "id": "words2 - 397",
        "front": "跳躍",
        "back": "도약"
    },
    {
        "id": "words2 - 398",
        "front": "逃亡",
        "back": "도망"
    },
    {
        "id": "words2 - 399",
        "front": "桃花",
        "back": "도화"
    },
    {
        "id": "words2 - 400",
        "front": "挑發",
        "back": "도발"
    },
    {
        "id": "words2 - 401",
        "front": "藥動",
        "back": "약동"
    }
]